// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The mean is:",
    answer: "The average of the numbers in a dataset",
    options: [
      "A nickname for your unfriendly friend",
      "The average of the numbers in a dataset",
      "The middle number in a dataset",
      "The most common number in a dataset"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following datasets has a variance of 0?",
    answer: "7, 7, 7, 7, 7",
    options: [
      "1, 2, 13, 2, 5",
      "5, 8, 0, 8, 2",
      "1, 2, 3, 4, 5",
      "7, 7, 7, 7, 7"
      
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "A parameter is:",
    answer: "A Population Characteristic",
    options: [
      "A Sample Characteristic",
      "A Population Characteristic",
      "Unknown",
      "Normal Normally Distributed"

    
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is an advantage of using volunteers in a study?",
    answer: "Volunteers are more willing to take part in the study ",
    options: [
      "Volunteer sampling guarantees a representative sample of the population",
      "Some volunteers do not complete the study",
      "Volunteers are more willing to take part in the study ",
      "Volunteer sampling prevents under coverage bias"
      
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which one of the following variables is NOT categorical?",
    answer: "Height of a Person",
    options: [
      "Age of a Person",
      "Gender of a Person: Male or Female",
      "Choice on a Test Item: True or False",
      "Height of a Person"

    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "A magazine printed a survey in its monthly issue and asked readers to fill it out and send it in. Over 1000 readers did so. This type of sample is called",
    answer: "A Self-Selected Sample",
    options: [
      "A Cluster Sample",
      "A Self-Selected Sample",
      "A Stratified Sample",
      "A Simple Random Sample"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which one of these statistics is unaffected by outliers?",
    answer: "Interquartile Range",
    options: [
      "Mean",
      "Interquartile Range",
      "Standard Deviation",
      "Range"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is a p-value?",
    answer: "None of the above",
    options: [
      "The probability of rejecting the null hypothesis ",
      "The probability of failing to reject the null hypothesis ",
      "The probability of a type one error",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "A sampling technique is used in Qualitative research wherein the researcher chooses individuals who are easily accessible to become respondents for the study.",
    answer: "Convenience Sampling",
    options: [
      "Judgement Sampling",
      "Convenience Sampling",
      "Snowball Sampling",
      "Quota Sampling"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Failing to reject the null hypothesis when it is false is:",
    answer: "Type II Error",
    options: [
      "Alpha",
      "Type I Error",
      "Type II Error",
      "Beta"
    ]
},
];